[
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_121",
        "question": "A 6 month old male presents to dermatology clinic for evaluation of skin depressions on the arms and legs present for a few months. <br>- The patient's mother denies any trauma that may have incited the depressions. <br>- Lesions are not painful or itchy to the patient. <br>- Mother denies any recent travel or treatments. <br>-   Past medical history is relevant for full term prenatal course. <br>- At birth, patient was noted to be red across the entire body with thin flaky yellow skin attached to the back and chest which slowly healed. <br>- Recently, patient was also evaluated by orthopaedics and completed a hand x-ray that showed epiphyseal stippling. <br>-   Physical examination is remarkable for multiple follicular based depressions a curvilinear distribution on the hands, legs, and feet on the hands, legs, and feet. <br>-  What is the most likely diagnosis?",
        "option1": "Rombo syndrome",
        "option2": "Conradi-Hünermann-Happle syndrome",
        "option3": "Bazex-Dupre-Christol syndrome",
        "option4": "Nicolau-Balus syndrome",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "82%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_132",
        "question": "A 45-year-old man presents to the primary care clinic with a red, itchy rash on the eyebrows and around the nose that has been ongoing for eight months. <br>- He has tried moisturizers to the areas, but the flakiness returns a few days later. <br>- He also reports he has dandruff in his scalp. <br>- He denies any new facial products or using any other creams or lotions. <br>-   Physical examination reveals greasy yellow scale on poorly demarcated erythematous patches on the eyebrows and bilateral nasal alar creases. <br>- Mild white scale is appreciated diffusely across the scalp.",
        "option1": "Seborrheic dermatitis",
        "option2": "Rosacea",
        "option3": "Acne vulgaris",
        "option4": "Psoriasis",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "79%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_028",
        "question": "The patient is a 13-year-old adolescent girl who presents with a 1-month history of a dark lesion on her finger. <br>- She states that the lesion does not bother her, but she came to the clinician because her mother was very concerned about the enlarging area of hyperpigmentation. <br>- The patient has no past medical history, no relevant family or social history, and is otherwise in good health. <br>- On examination, the rash appears to be a 1 x 1 cm circular patch of hyperpigmentation with overlying scale on the middle finger. <br>- During the past month, the rash has grown in size but remains asymptomatic.",
        "option1": "Tinea nigra",
        "option2": "Lentigines",
        "option3": "Acral melanoma",
        "option4": "Acral nevi",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "59%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_108",
        "question": "A 72-year-old woman is seen by the Dermatology consult service for a rash which has developed during a prolonged 6-week hospitalization following a hemorrhagic stroke. <br>- She is currently intubated, so history is limited, but per chart review, nurses documented the rash starting 5 days ago. <br>- She has been experiencing high fevers as well as unexplained transaminitis over the last few days. <br>- She has taken atorvastatin and pantoprazole for years, including during the hospitalization. <br>- Following the stroke, she was started on carbamazepine for seizure prophylaxis. <br>- She contracted MRSA pneumonia 2 weeks ago and has been on vancomycin since then. <br>- She has also been on cefepime and micafungin for the last 5 days given the fevers and transaminitis. <br>- Physical examination is significant for diffuse erythematous patches extending over the face, chest, back, and extremities, as well as facial edema.",
        "option1": "Stevens-Johnson Syndrome",
        "option2": "Drug reaction with eosinophilia and systemic symptoms",
        "option3": "Morbilliform drug eruption",
        "option4": "Lichenoid drug eruption",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "58%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_067",
        "question": "A 68-year-old white man presents with 4 weeks of progressively worsening thickening of the skin and plaques on the bilateral nipple and areola. <br>- He has no personal or family history of warts or epidermal nevi and has not had hormonal therapy. <br>- On examination, he has hyperpigmented, verrucous plaques bilaterally, with no associated erythema or lymphadenopathy. <br>- Skin biopsy shows hyperkeratosis with papillomatosis. <br>- Corticosteroid treatment failed, but there was some minor improvement with calcipotriol after several weeks of use.",
        "option1": "Chronic eczema",
        "option2": "Nipple hyperkeratosis",
        "option3": "Acanthosis nigricans",
        "option4": "Darier disease",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "88%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_065",
        "question": "An elderly man presents with asymptomatic hyperpigmented, confluent, brown macules on his upper and lower lips, along with hyperpigmented macules on his hands. <br>- He also has diffuse blue-black bilateral melanonychia with nail dystrophy on his toenails, and his fingernails contain longitudinal melanonychia with hyperpigmentation of the proximal nail beds. <br>- He denies any family history of mucocutaneous pigmentation or gastrointestinal or systemic symptoms. <br>- In the last 5 years, results of a colonoscopy, upper gastrointestinal endoscopy, and blood work have all been within normal limits.",
        "option1": "Peutz-Jeghers syndrome",
        "option2": "Bandler syndrome",
        "option3": "McCune-Albright syndrome",
        "option4": "Laugier-Hunziker syndrome",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "93%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_041",
        "question": "A 30-year-old healthy Hispanic woman presents with a slowly progressive facial deformity present since early childhood. <br>- She denies any new lesions during this time, any history of trauma to the area, and any family history of similar skin lesions. <br>- Examination reveals a bulging, deformed dermal mass with a “bag-of-worms” appearance involving the upper right quadrant of her face, with hypertrophy of the overlying skin and soft tissues. <br>- Neurofibromas and café-au-lait macules are not observed.",
        "option1": "Plexiform neurofibroma",
        "option2": "Schwannomas",
        "option3": "Eczema herpeticum",
        "option4": "Synovial sarcoma",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "67%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_082",
        "question": "A 65-year-old man of Middle Eastern descent presents with a tender, weeping mass on his right palm. <br>- Since appearing 8 months ago, the lesion has enlarged into a 0.9-cm, pink pedunculated nodule with abundant serous crust. <br>- The patient has no significant history of trauma. <br>- His medical history is significant for atrial fibrillation, hypertension, coronary artery disease, congestive heart failure, and lung cancer, which was treated with right lobectomy. <br>- It is unclear what medications were used to treat his lung cancer. <br>- His current medications include metoprolol, lisinopril, allopurinol, aspirin, and digoxin. <br>- The patient also presents with additional pink, scaly plaques on his right ankle, consistent with nummular eczema.",
        "option1": "Amelanotic melanoma",
        "option2": "Lobular capillary hemangioma",
        "option3": "Bacillary angiomatosis",
        "option4": "Squamous cell carcinoma",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "46%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_001",
        "question": "A 51-year-old white man presents to the clinic with a 2-year history of a painful, recurrent rash on his fingers. <br>- He initially noticed redness, irritation, and pustules around his nails that he thought were caused by an infection. <br>- However, the rash progressed to affect the nail bed, eventually destroying his nails. <br>- On examination, well-demarcated, scaly plaques with associated pustules and nail atrophy are present on the right second and third distal digits. <br>- He is otherwise healthy.",
        "option1": "Acrodermatitis continua of Hallopeau",
        "option2": "Herpetic whitlow",
        "option3": "Paronychia",
        "option4": "Acute contact dermatitis",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "80%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_093",
        "question": "A 28-year-old Black man presents with a 2-year history of dyspigmentation of his back and chest. <br>- The patient notes that the lesions initially had red borders but these have faded over the past several months. <br>- Physical examination reveals circular, ashy-gray macules distributed diffusely over his back and chest. <br>- The patient denies pain or pruritus and takes nomedication. <br>- He notes that he recently traveled to Mexico. <br>- He has been relatively unconcerned about the lesions and only sought medical care to rule out cancer.",
        "option1": "Fixed-drug eruption",
        "option2": "Macular amyloidosis",
        "option3": "Erythema dyschromicum perstans",
        "option4": "Addison disease",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "85%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_037",
        "question": "A 56-year-old man presents with diffuse pruritic papules involving the upper body, with nose and forehead thickening. <br>- Over the past 2 years, he has been evaluated by multiple specialists for dysphagia, reflux, chronic kidney disease, hypertension, and dyspnea on exertion. <br>- Examination results are significant for generalized firm, fleshy, dome-shaped papules of several millimeters in diameter, on his forehead, ears, neck, trunk, back, proximal upper extremities, and dorsal hands, with forehead, glabella, and nose induration. <br>- Relevant laboratory findings include monoclonal gammopathy on serum immunofixation, consisting of immunoglobulin (Ig) G_ and IgA_, and unremarkable thyroid panel findings",
        "option1": "Scleroderma",
        "option2": "Nephrogenic systemic fibrosis",
        "option3": "Scleromyxedema",
        "option4": "Scleredema",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "65%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_064",
        "question": "A man, aged 68 years, with no known history of atopy presents with a 4-month history of an itchy and burning rash on the legs that has been recurring every winter for the past 3 years. <br>- He notes that he had dry skin at baseline and did not use emollients, but he did try hydrocortisone 1% cream without improvement. <br>- Examination revealed ovoid, erythematous, well-marginated plaques on the lower legs and dorsal feet with variable scaling and focal weeping and crusting. <br>- There were no nail changes, and the rest of his skin examination was notable only for xerosis.",
        "option1": "Psoriasis",
        "option2": "Nummular dermatitis",
        "option3": "Tinea corporis",
        "option4": "Bullous impetigo",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "76%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_046",
        "question": "A 60-year-old man presents with rapidly growing lesions on his face, trunk, axillae, flexural areas, and groin. <br>- The lesions appeared 3 months earlier in his perianal area and extended rapidly to other areas. <br>- Previously, he was treated with topical agents for atopic dermatitis and seborrheic dermatitis without improvement. <br>- Examination reveals disseminated violaceous papules and plaques on the face, trunk, axillae, and perianal area; some lesions were confluent and ulcerated. <br>- Yellowish-red to skin-colored papules are present on the scalp. <br>- He has no palpable lymphadenopathy or organomegaly.",
        "option1": "Prurigo nodularis",
        "option2": "Atopic dermatitis",
        "option3": "Seborrheic dermatitis",
        "option4": "Cutaneous Langerhans cell histiocytosis",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "53%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_050",
        "question": "A healthy 15-year-old girl presents with a solitary, asymptomatic lesion on her back. <br>- The lesion has been present since birth but has enlarged over the past 2 years. <br>- She denies association with previous trauma and irritation. <br>- Examination reveals multiple, comedo-like openings filled with dark lamellate keratinocyte plugs grouped in a linear distribution over a slightly hypotrophic area of 3 cm by 7 cm. <br>- Dermoscopy revealed numerous circular and barrel-shaped homogenous areas in dark-brown shades with remarkable keratin plugs.",
        "option1": "Segmental acne",
        "option2": "Nevus comedonicus",
        "option3": "Trichofolliculoma",
        "option4": "Familial dyskeratotic comedones",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "74%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_061",
        "question": "A 55-year-old black man presents for evaluation of fine wrinkles that had developed over the past year. <br>- Physical examination reveals diffuse areas offine wrinkling that run parallel to lines of cleavage on his neck, chest, axilla, trunk, back, and upper arms bilaterally. <br>- The affected skin has normal pigmentation and lacks erythema, induration, and atrophy. <br>- Lateral tension obliterates the wrinkling. <br>- The patient never notes any inflammation, itching, or pain. <br>- There are no signs or symptoms of systemic involvement. <br>- He denies sunbathing and denies any history of skin disorders or other significant health problems.",
        "option1": "Marshall syndrome",
        "option2": "Perifollicular elastolysis",
        "option3": "Anetoderma",
        "option4": "Mid-dermal elastolysis",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "56%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    }
]